Thank you for watching!
How are you?
The "Halo! Stee, this time with Morning Musume.' 24's Reina Yokoyama and
I am Honoka Kobayashi from Beyond Seasonings.
Please stay with us until the end of this issue, as we will be presenting you with two such people.
We don't really communicate on social networking sites,
We actually go out to eat and hang out in private quite a bit.
Actually.
I forget to take a picture every time,
It's just too much fun.
Yokoyama-san is always asking me for advice,
Thank you for the opportunity to talk with you about all of this.
It's my pleasure.
I hope we can play again this year.
We will definitely invite you back.
Please.
And now, Hello! Project 2024 Winter 3 of Us is underway.
We're going around in two teams,
The first 24, Beyonds, and Tsubaki Factory are all part of one team that we are rotating around,
It's soooo fun and enjoyable, isn't it?
That's what the members did, even during rehearsals, by getting everyone excited.
That's because the members of Beyonds are very bright,
They make rehearsals exciting with great energy.
That's why I'm having a lot of fun from the rehearsals.
If I said that, Morning Musume。 Morning Musume。
I'll be standing and cheering for you.
He stood up and cheered us on.
I really feel cheerful from the rehearsals.
The atmosphere is so great that I really hate to see the tour end now.
Now please watch this video.
Go ahead!
Start! Crane! Tange! Jump! Go!
The best meal ever. Beyon, beyon, beyon, beyon.
Come on, rap and jump for real.
To you, my dear Dibon Dibon.
The best meal. Beyon, beyon, beyon.
I wanted to look good in style.
One size fits all, shoulder duplication
I saw you and your girlfriend.
A love that is unknown, fleeting, and scattered
Open to page
The battle to Heisei 5.
Let's all stop. Let's go wild.
Line O!
To the next future, to the next era
JUMP SHOW! Jump show! Jump show!
Three, two, one, seriously!
Let's have a tayogara to the Heisei days.
Take your time with momentum and how you ride.
Leiwa! Leiwa! Leiwa! Long.
Best timing
What are you doing? Anniversary.
Let's hope.
Combined! Combination! Whatever.
Combined! Combined! Combined! Whatever.
Come on, rap and jump for real.
Here's today's meal. Beyon, beyon, beyon.
Ribbon Ribbon to a new day
Come on, rap and jump for real.
Here's today's meal. Beyon, beyon, beyon.
You don't know. First year of the Showa Era.
something that was not certain
serious (not capricious or flirtatious)
You don't know. 1989.
The regular stipulation of 3%.
Oh, that's right.
Digital natives: The power of the Heisei-born
Let's connect with each other and make it better.
Hey now!
Next year. Next future.
Jump show!
Let's say good-bye to the days of calm.
Point confidence is important.
Never, never, never. Wait. Best Lady.
exactly what one has to do
Let's go beyond ourselves.
Because it's an easy year.
The train with that handsome Mr. Glasses on it is about to arrive.
Wow! I'm so excited!
There are many rivals, but we can't lose!
That's right! Juhane has a bright future ahead of her.
Take a peek! What future do you see?
Wow, that wasn't me!
Glasses!
Even if I could live on the moon or go back in time.
We're not trying too hard. We're just trying to keep it together.
Great!
To the future that is.
Forever to an era like this.
Just show!
3, 2, 1, party!
To the days of calm.
Let's say goodbye.
Momentum and position won.
Day one! Day one! Let's go!
Hey great timing!
anniversary of what you did
I want to be happy.
Because effortless hearts.
Because it's easy and mangy.
Because it's easy.
Come on, easy and real jump.
Let's try today's meal.
Your favorite Pom Pom Pom
Come on, easy and real jump.
Let's try today's meal.
I'll be rooting for you anytime! Fight!
Morning Musume。 14's Reina Yokoyama and Yoshi Kobayashi of Yeons Seasonings present "Halo! Ste.
I'm going to ask you a few questions, so don't think too much, just answer them at a quick pace.
Okay? I'll do my best! Okay, I'll get right to it.
Yoshi, born in the year of the Tatsu, what song from Hello Project do you think will be your theme song this year?
Morning Musume。' 23's Wake up call When you wake up Last December was the 5th anniversary of joining the BEYONES.
What has been the most impactful moment for you in the past five years? Recently, I met Mr. ZUNK for the first time.
What do you do to stay in shape during this cold and dry season?
Sleeping with a scarf.
Hello Kitty, what kitty goods did you get recently? I got an acrylic keychain with a picture of a stuffed animal from Ka-Utano Sato of the Beyonce's.
What kind of year is 2024 going to be for Beyoncé? I think it will be a year in which we will be able to show you the new Beyoncé.
It's over! I was so nervous! I was so nervous, but I think I did a great job answering the questions!
Then can I ask you a few questions about what I'm wondering about? First of all.
The Hello Project song that will be my theme song this year is Morning Musume.' 13's Makeup Call When You Wake Up
I'm so happy! I've been listening to it a lot lately, but when I listen to it live, I'm listening to it in a very dynamic acoustic environment.
I enjoy the sound of your voices and the bass, but when I listen to it through earphones, I hear a lot of different harmonies.
I'm really into it when I realize that the melody is played in such harmony.
But it is true that we and Morning Musume。 But it's true that when we sang this song, we wanted to give the impression that we were rapping and that we were really cool, but we also wanted to give the impression that we were really cool, too.
The lyrics of the songs are very deep, and I am very happy that they were chosen because I want to convey those lyrics in my performance.
Thank you. And one more thing I was wondering about is the importance of taking care of yourself.
Can I just ask one more time? Sleep with your scarf on.
It's the first I've heard of it, and I kind of don't remember why I remembered to wear a scarf to bed.
If you keep your neck warm, you're less likely to catch a cold or something. Yeah, I know, they say that's important.
I thought my neck might be cold when I sleep, so I wrapped the circuit around my neck and there is a circuit of collars.
Oh, yeah, wrap that around and then wrap a scarf over it, it'll keep you warm.
I'm sleeping with my hood up and tucked in. Wow, it's like the style that people out there do, it's like total oblivion.
I'm doing it under the covers, but it sounds really warming.
I'm sure it's perfect when you wear a mask. We still have a lot of concerts to go, after all.
I got some really good questions, thank you very much.
Questions for Mr. Yokoyama after the VTR
Hallo! Ste.
GETCHU!
Maybe it's the summer.
Bach-chang, bach-chang, bach-chang, bach-chang, bach-chang, bach-chang, bach-chang, bach-chang, tea horse
Tea Horse 1st album Channel 1 now on sale!
Hallo! Ste.
Next, I would like to ask Mr. Yokoyama a question.
Yes, I will do my best to answer. I will do my best to answer.
Now I would like to get started.
The day after tomorrow, it will be 7 whole years since the official blog for the 13th term started. The post that you should definitely read is ?
I'm embarrassed to say this, but first post!
How would you like to end your 22nd year?
Anyway, I would like to close with the thought that I had a good time.
What do you want this winter?
I want a kotatsu again this year.
What do you do when you feel like you're going to catch a cold?
Anyway, I go outside and walk a lot.
It has been about two months since the new organization was formed. How would you describe the current Morning Musume。 24 in one word?
Once again, we go back to the beginning.
Thank you very much.
Nervous.
The spirited part.
Thank you very much.
I'd like to draw your attention to something I've been wondering about, though,
I want you to read the very first blog.
I was really worried about it,
The very first blog right after you join is,
It's a little embarrassing, isn't it? I am.
However, it is a true feeling only after joining the group,
I was into this stuff at this time,
I wanted people to discover that Yokoyama liked this kind of thing,
I'm a little embarrassed about my very first blog,
I thought I'd like you to read it.
I would like to read it too.
Embarrassing.
We would very much appreciate it.
And one more thing I want this winter.
Yes.
Kotatsu.
It's cold, isn't it?
It's cold, really cold already.
I wanted it every year.
You want it every year?
That's really it.
I have also said this in a Halloween party quite a few years ago. I had the opportunity to say this at the Halo!
He wants a kotatsu.
I'll buy a kotatsu this year," he said,
It's been maybe two years.
Oops.
I'm probably saying.
Hallo! Ste.
But it's hard to find the time to buy,
I think I had time to buy it,
I knew it!
Spirits.
Buying something big takes a lot of energy, doesn't it?
I've noticed that it's been a long month,
This is the year,
Get a little kotatsu,
I'd like to get warm and cozy.
I will report back. If I buy it.
Please try to buy one this year.
Yes, I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'll buy it.
Hallo! Ste. It will continue after this.
Natsuyaki Masa
I am Masashi Natsuyaki.
Here we go, Hello Kitchen.
This time we had a member here.
I am Shori Nishida from Beyond!
I would like to enjoy cooking with my teacher.
I will do my best. Best regards.
Thank you for your time, doctor.
Yes, I would like to know if you have any questions or comments. Thank you very much for your cooperation.
What will you make this time?
Today's dish is pork and cheese millefeuille style.
Looks delicious.
The materials will be here.
Do you cook, Nishida-chan?
It is not that I don't do it at all, but I do it at least in moderation.
It looks promising.
Let's have fun cooking.
I will do my best.
Please.
So, what would you like to do first, doctor?
First of all, I would like to make the tomato sauce again!
When I think of tomato sauce, I think of onions.
100 g onion
I'm really not a fan of onions, they're my favorite food to cut.
I couldn't stop crying and sniffling.
certainly and certainly
They're going to get hit.
You're gonna get your ass handed to you.
Have you ever used a knife?
Yes, sir.
I'm not sure.
I don't have confidence.
Zero confidence is zero.
But I don't dislike the dish itself.
Yes, sir.
I'll put the next one in.
Let's put it in.
Yes, sir.
Garlic.
Peel and split in half.
I've never touched garlic before.
Really?
Yes, sir.
In a balanced state and at an angle.
diagonally
Yes, sir.
See you in the next video!
We'll crush it.
I'll try.
If you don't go in the middle, you'll get crushed.
Here we go.
heave, ho!
gentle
Here we go.
more
Great.
Scrape through a colander
tomato
spike
You can do it with something like a whipper.
It's coming our way quite nicely.
pressing or rubbing with turning movements (e.g. someone's shoulders with one's elbow)
That's rather kind of you.
Yeah, something like that.
It's weak. It's not strong enough.
With a spatula.
these last (followed by a duration noun and a past sentence: time period before the present time of the speaker)
It's what's left down there.
You took it clean off.
Yes, sir.
I think I got it.
Thank you.
Now, let's get to it!
Sauce making.
First, 3 tablespoons of olive oil.
About 50 cc.
Then I'll put some garlic here.
All of them?
All of them.
Keep the pan at an angle.
If you do this, the garlic will float and the aroma will not transfer.
With all the oil used in the oil as much as possible.
I can see bubbles coming out of it.
Then we gradually reduce the heat to low.
This garlic
The bottom is on fire.
Please turn over.
It's colored.
If you don't turn off the heat and just go with it...
It burns in the blink of an eye.
This is already a nice touch, honestly.
That's a great first time.
Stir-fried.
In the central part of the country, the aroma doesn't come out this much.
This oil is full of garlic flavor.
Onions here.
Is this medium heat?
This is done over medium heat at first.
You don't have to touch it too much.
If you spread it out...
I prefer to hit the pan as much as possible.
This color is important.
Tomato sauce is the best here.
Is it important?
With curry.
Now it's time to decide.
I'm afraid I'm going to have to stop you.
I guess it's time to put out the fire.
It's already in the doldrums.
And put this in.
tomato
And this one, too. Drop it around and you'll be fine.
I don't need to touch it too much.
We have a surprising amount of time here.
The idea is to let the sauce simmer for about 10 minutes.
I hope we can talk about our activities here.
Use these 10 minutes.
What are you doing as Beyooooonds these days?
As for the Beyooooonds, the Hello Project concert is taking place this winter.
Morning Musume。 24 and Tsubaki Factory and Beyooooonds are in the middle of finishing their tour.
What is the difference between doing it with just the Beyooooonds and doing it now with those three groups?
Beyooooonds is a group that has never had a graduation join yet.
Yes, indeed.
I don't have any juniors.
So, I've seen younger members of the group grow up, and I've seen other members of the group grow up, and I've been impressed by the growth of other members of the group.
Recently, Haruka Inoue, a 17th term member of Morning Musume。 24's 17th term member, Haruka Inoue, and the girl who ran away from the group, it was really nice to meet her on the tour.
I saw her smile and her facial expression was very beautiful.
I really enjoy noticing those little changes because I'm with you every time.
You're watching very closely.
I like it.
I keep looking at the other teams.
It's not easy to look a little and feel growth.
And that's what you're doing while you're still active.
Because you have a lot of your own things to do.
Singing and dancing
even
I think about the team, after all.
that's so, isn't it
I'm sure there is.
But other than that, it's great to get out to the juniors on other teams.
But quite a bit.
I'm here while you're doing that.
How's it going?
Come here, come here, come here. Put a little garlic back in there.
It's changing color and stuff.
It's different.
It certainly looks orangey.
And... oil floats in the air.
certainly
We're running out of water.
Not quite.
About three or four minutes.
Shall we go?
Yes, sir.
Yes, it has changed quite a bit already.
I asked him to taste it a little, and he said, "I hardly put any salt on it,
Just the right amount.
Yes.
Strong tomato taste.
It is an amazing tomato.
It's insanely delicious.
It has a sour taste, though,
That kind of flying is already happening, isn't it?
I think all the acidity is turning into sweetness, and it's getting darker, so,
In this state, though, it's totally delicious, like pasta,
It's almost like a main dish today,
I'd like to try a little bit.
Yes.
Here, Miyamizu Point!
The sauce is to be smooth.
Here it is.
Something came up.
Appearance.
Use this,
Suddenly?
I let them come in with a little bit of oil or something floating in them,
Incoming.
It's Italian, isn't it?
It's pretty zany.
It's like by doing this, it becomes more French.
Amazing.
Teacher!
Are you okay?
Even though there was a little clump of garlic.
I have to crush garlic.
It was very dangerous.
Teacher!
Direct hit!
Direct hit on the teacher!
It is a direct hit on the teacher.
It's okay.
Is the teacher dirty and nothing?
Sorry.
It's totally fine.
This is said to fly unexpectedly.
This is no longer a good idea.
Amazing.
It looks soooo good.
Looks delicious.
Amazing.
Would you like to taste it?
I liked it a lot.
I mean, to this kind of tenderness.
This is absolutely delicious.
Amazing.
Oh no.
This is all it takes. Absolutely.
The mouth feel is totally different.
That's fine.
Then this is perfect now.
Yes.
So that's all for this time.
Thank you very much.
Yes, it is.
So, let's do our best as it will be completed next time.
I will do my best.
Amazing.
Dream.
But it's amazing. Nice browning.
It's true. I saw it for a moment, now.
Nice.
We will take it.
This is...
Funny...
Looks delicious, no really, it makes me hungry, really, it looks super yummy.
I'm looking forward to seeing it completed. I'm looking forward to seeing it completed.
Houkachan is a cook, a cook, a cook.
I can do it, but I won't do it. I'm that type of person. I can do it. I can do it.
I could do it if I wanted to, but this is the only thing I really want to do.
There's a dish I'm really good at that I want to show you... grilled sausage.
Grilled sausages, grilled sausages, you know, when you go to a barbecue or a barbecue, there are sausages, right?
But with vegetables, when you realize you've overcooked them, you can't help but think, "I've overcooked them a little bit.
I think there is, but I've never done anything like that before.
They are so good at baking! They are crispy on the outside and juicy on the inside.
So if there is anyone who would like me to make a bento like this, I will be happy to do so, even if you are a member.
I can make grilled sausages. I'm looking forward to it.
I was buried in making omelets for a while.
So I'm not sure if I can do it now, but I'll use that pan and make it fluffy inside.
I'm really good at making that nice, soft, chewy outside, the kind of thing I've always wanted to make.
You mean with cheese? I mean, you can cook with it.
If I wanted to, I could do it. Besides, it's an omelette, right? I can make sausages.
You didn't just buy breakfast? Surely, if you bought some bread and laid it out, you'd have a very nice breakfast.
Elegant breakfast. We can cook.
Hallo! Ste.
Morning Musume。 24's Reina Yokoyama and Honoko Kobayashi of Beyonce's Seasonings present "Halo! Ste.
In the current Hello! Project 2024 Winter 3 of Us, we are performing with the same team.
We have a lot of opportunities to see each other's performances, but, uh, what do you think?
I really love Morning Musume。 Tsubaki Factory has been making new songs and new and wonderful things every time.
I love the performance of Bjorns, and I also love the performance of Tsubaki Factory, so I'm really learning every day.
Although they are the same idols, the three groups have completely different concepts and themes.
I always think it's a lot of fun to discover new things.
This time, we have selected some live videos from the other group's music that we would like to recommend, and we would like to introduce them to you in this order.
Yes! First of all, I, Yokoyama, would like to recommend a song by BEYONES, "Seek Me, Destiny's Traveler"!
I really love this song, but this time I would like to show you a biophonic video.
First of all, I'd like you to look at this moment, but my favorite point is that...
The more people in a group, the more important it is to have the right amount of depth in the formation.
The orchestra is in the back for this concert, so the depth is a little narrower than in a regular concert hall.
Yes, and in this situation, it's dangerous to bump into the back of the car as well.
It's really cool to see how well they can perform together, you know, and you can see that they're doing this formation and that formation, and they're watching their backs.
When I think about it, I really have a lot of respect for him.
Also, please look here, here.
I thought it was really cool that all the members were jumping so high, but when I saw this for the first time, I thought it was really cool.
I knew that when I was going to play with the orchestra, I didn't want to jump as far as I could this time.
I was wondering if you had discussed this with everyone.
As you can see, the stage is a tree. Yes, it is.
If we fly off like we usually do, all 12 of us will fly off at once, and we've been thinking since rehearsal that we're going to go boom.
If that happens, we'll do this.
I was really looking forward to seeing the collaboration with the orchestra and wondering what kind of feeling it would have,
I used to play alto saxophone and other instruments in orchestras, so I was able to see the formation performances and sounds that are possible only with orchestras,
I learned a lot from the collaboration of an idol and an orchestra, which was really cool.
How was it? What did you think of the collaboration?
This was the first time for me to perform an entire concert, but it was the second time for me to collaborate with an orchestra,
I see.
We all worked together on that first improvement exhibition, and Mr. Seinoh also made improvements,
We were able to rehearse and discuss how we would perform on the small stage,
I think we became more united and learned more about music.
It was very cool.
Thank you very much.
Next, I would like to recommend Morning Musume。 s songs are,
Monright Night. It's a moonlit night.
In this issue of Morning Musume。 23 Concert Tour Autumn NEVER ENDING Employee Award 3 Couture - Sei Fukumura Graduation Special' video together.
I would like to recommend Morning Musume。 Morning Musume,
Monright Night. It's a moonlit night.
In this issue of Morning Musume。 23 Concert Tour Autumn NEVER ENDING Employee Award 3 Couture - Sei Fukumura Graduation Special' video together.
Wow cool.
The menace of this song is amazing.
I thought it was great.
It looks good on you.
The moment they came out, I was watching them thinking, wow, this is great,
Yakinumiya, Rio Kitagawa, Mei Yamazaki and Rio Koryo.
Everyone is doing it, but with a really powerful balance,
What are your thoughts, Mr. Tanaka?
Yes. The choreography of my impressions was also created from scratch by the teacher,
Choreograph this as if the two of you are going to confront each other,
The teacher even made it for this tour.
You can really feel the power of the dance even when you are far away.
On the contrary, everyone was singing in the same voice they had met,
It's wonderful. Really.
It's also a song that fans can shout out and get excited with,
It feels great to do it live,
I think it's really cool because it increases the power.
It's a group of people who have a great visual when they are in the vision.
I'm sure you all do,
They are all beautiful.
You are using it well,
Love this last part!
Cool end!
I really love it.
This time the video was from a concert held at Yokohama Arena,
I really had a chance to spectate that day too,
Thank you very much.
There were so many wonderful moments besides this song,
Glad to hear it.
I was really confused,
Among them, I was allowed to choose the most impressive one that I saw at that time.
Glad to hear it.
Mr. Yokoyama also sang Agulara with Jacquelin,
It is the best part of a solo tour,
Performing a song with a small group is one part of the tour that fans look forward to,
But it was really cool.
Really.
Now the video.
When the last image of Makino-san was shown,
I was like, "I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I've been here for a long time.
It was very powerful.
It was really cool, really cool.
I would like to see many more in the future.
Thank you very much.
Now for the really last song.
We're all in this together.
Come on, Mirai.
Run!
Let's get excited about the last Budokan!
At the end of the road that ran through the kinky shuffle.
He's stroking a chafing wound to gauge the distance.
Straightforward ideals and nervous disposition
Looking back, it was a series of detours.
Throw away your pride and try again.
If you're lost, this is where you start.
Now, run along and put your heart and soul into it.
My skates are gonna get turned up, but I don't care about that.
than I was back then.
If only I could be a little stronger.
The next era begins
I'm sure it's in our future.
Juice Juice Juice Juice
Minutes later, time passes and we forget.
I've kept my strength, my lies, and my love in a box.
A real commitment, yes, but a quiet one.
Through the gap in your bangs. The future you're staring at.
If clumsiness is now only the beauty of the identel
It doesn't matter if it's a little snarky, let's go with natural.
The sound of running hard into the palm of my hand and kicking at the dirt echoes through the air.
Go jump over that paddle
Let's carve out a new era.
If you need another forecast.
You can come back here.
We will rise again and again.
Let's go, our future
Juice-Juice
People who love Juice-Juice because of Juice-Juice.
Raise your voice.
Even now, start running.
Put your thoughts on your toes.
It's a skirt that's going to turn up.
They don't care about that.
than I am.
I guess I'm a little stronger.
The next light begins.
Live our future
Tubing Tubing
thank you very much
It was Juice-Juice!
Thanks for everything. I'm rooting for you too.
Morning Musume。 24's Rena Yokoyama and Beyonce Seasonings' Honoka Kobayashi present "Halo! Ste.
It's time for us to say goodbye, and here's an announcement.
Hello Project 2024 Winter 3ofus is now underway!
Morning Musume。 24Beyons is traveling around the country as Team A with Tsubaki Factory
The next one will be at Aichi Park on January 27th, so please come and visit us if you are in the area.
Beyonc will be at Hello Music Festival 2024 in Tokyo on February 4.
We will be performing with Halo Pro trainee unit 2Four.
And the Blu-ray of the Drama Women's Club Beauty Spy Disappearing Attache Case.
It will be released in spring 2024. Please pick up a copy!
And Morning Musume。 23 25th Anniversary Concert Tour
Grad Quarter Century at Nippon Budokan Blu-ray DVD will be released on February 7!
It was a very exciting concert, so I was very excited to be a part of it.
I hope you will take a look at it.
Carbon Neutrality 2024 by Satoyama Satomi Movement will be held at Makuhari Messe on March 30 and 31!
Please come visit us!
Hello! Project is a channel where the members of Hello!
New videos will be uploaded every Wednesday, so please subscribe to our channel!
This time we were joined by Rena Yokoyama of Morning Musume。 24 and Honoka Kobayashi of Nions Seasonings.
good-bye